<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: Presentation | Utopian Computing]]></title>
  <link href="http://UtopianComputing.github.io/blog/categories/presentation/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://UtopianComputing.github.io/"/>
  <updated>2014-08-15T16:31:05-03:00</updated>
  <id>http://UtopianComputing.github.io/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Ben Langfeld]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Quality Software Engineering for Your Data Center]]></title>
    <link href="http://UtopianComputing.github.io/blog/2014/08/14/quality-software-engineering-for-your-data-center/"/>
    <updated>2014-08-14T22:16:23-03:00</updated>
    <id>http://UtopianComputing.github.io/blog/2014/08/14/quality-software-engineering-for-your-data-center</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>In two weeks, Ben Langfeld will present at <a href="http://www.rubyconf.com.br/">RubyConf Brasil</a> for the third time. &ldquo;Quality software engineering for your data center&rdquo; is up at 13:15 on 28th August 2014 at the Frei Caneca Theatre, São Paulo.</p>

<p>DevOps is the melding of minds between the development/engineering and operations communities to form a super-discipline with the best of the experience of both sides as a force for stability, flexibility, efficiency and agility in the management of large-scale application or service deployments. DevOps is about automating out day-to-day monotony, and then going further to bridge many of the things operations people are used to doing manually with the best-practices developed on the other side of the fence, particularly around automated testing and agility.</p>

<p>Go! But wait a minute! That&rsquo;s not enough for everyone to know what they should be doing, you say. You&rsquo;re right, it&rsquo;s not. There is a wealth of information on specific DevOps issues on the internet, and some good introductory material, but few comprehensive, opinionated overviews of what you <em>should</em> do. This talk will solve that problem and have you 100% ready to embark on or fix-up your DevOps journey to blissful nights sleep while rocking regular new features for your users.</p>

<p>We&rsquo;ll talk Puppet &amp; Chef, testing and turbulence, robots and thermo-nuclear weapons. If you&rsquo;ve just started with DevOps and need to know what you need to know, or have been muddling for a little while with some Puppets but the show always turns into a fight, then this is for you!</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
